

Pittimon Rungrojpathomporn

Frontend Developer

61010822@kmitl.ac.th 0917799819

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Vue

Profile

My nickname is Pink. I was born in Ratchaburi on 1 January 2000. I have experience in web development in the field of frontend development. I really enjoy learning about coding knowledge, and have growth mindset. I want to be a part of the organization that provides me a challenging job which helps me achieve personal as well as organizational goals

Experience

Jun 2021 — Dec 2022

Internship at SILKSPAN INSURANCE BROKERAGE COMPANY Ltd.

- · Create a incentiveaivepenalty website with vue.js
- Create reusable components demotablevuejs with vue.js
- Develop recievecanclesaluklung use .net with junior developer team
- Develop changepremiumregist use .net with junior developer team

2022

Personal Website

- · Create personal website with react.js
- · https://resume-ptm.herokuapp.com/

Nov 2021 — Apr 2022

Restaurant Reservations

- Create restaurant reservations website with vuejs and firebase
- https://reservation-1137b.web.app/

2020

Dechosanpe

- · Create a web application with react and firebase
- https://dechosanpe.web.app

Education

2018 - 2022

King Mongkut's University of Technology Ladkrabang

Bachelor of Engineering, Major Information Engineering

GPA: 3.2